(Penny:)Helium.
(Sheldon:)Yes.
Yes.
(Sheldon:)Taylor Swift.
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Penny:)Pi.
(Sheldon:)Kardashian.
(Penny:)More specific.
(Sheldon:)Khloe?
Yes!
(Sheldon:)See, I remembered
(Sheldon:)because if it looks
like Kim it's Kim,
(Sheldon:)if it looks kind of
like Kim it's Kourtney,
(Sheldon:)and if it looks nothing
like Kim it's Khloe.
(Penny:)Oh.
(Penny:)Oh,
(Penny:)that's a Venn Diagram,
and I remember because
(Penny:)I thought to myself,
“Venn is he gonna stop
talking about this diagram?”
(Leonard:)What are you guys doing?
Oh, well,
(Sheldon:)we decided to use
our breakfast time
(Sheldon:)to expand our respective
knowledge bases.
(Leonard:)Oh, let me try.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Leonard:)Hmm, atom of hydrogen,
Adam of Maroon 5, mic drop.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry,
who is Mike Drop?